var config = {
    "numCategories": 5,
    "numQuestionsPerCategory": 5,
    "numTeams": 4,
    "saveLocation": "~/Desktop/",
    "password": "lebronjames",
    "currentTeam": "test1",
    "teams": [
        {
            "name": "test1"
        },
        {
            "name": "test2"
        },
        {
            "name": "test3"
        },
        {
            "name": "test4"
        }
    ],
    "data": {
        "FAMILY": [
            {
                "question": "THE MEANING OF MURUGAN'S NAME",
                "answer": "WHO IS GOD",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 100
            },
            {
                "question": "AGE GAP BETWEEN NITYA AND HIM",
                "answer": "WHAT IS 4 YEARS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 200
            },
            {
                "question": "SCHOOL THAT NITYA GRADUATED FROM",
                "answer": "WHAT IS OLIN",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 300
            },
            {
                "question": "# OF HOUSES MURUGAN HAS LIVED IN",
                "answer": "WHAT IS 3 HOUSES",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 400
            },
            {
                "question": "MEANING OF MURUGAN'S LAST NAME",
                "answer": "WHAT IS AN ABANDONED SMALL TOWN IN SOUTHERN TIP OF INDIA",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 500
            }
        ],
        "NBA": [
            {
                "question": "MURUGANS'S FAVORITE NBA PLAYER",
                "answer": "WHO IS LEBRON JAMES",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 100
            },
            {
                "question": "NBA TEAM MURUGAN SUPPORTED FIRST",
                "answer": "WHAT IS LA LAKERS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 200
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S MOST HATED TEAM",
                "answer": "WHAT IS WARRIORS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 300
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S LEAST LIKED PLAYER",
                "answer": "WHO IS CURRY",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 400
            },
            {
                "question": "PLAYER ON MURUGAN'S FIRST JERSEY",
                "answer": "WHO IS ALLEN IVERSON",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 500
            }
        ],
        "SCHOOL": [
            {
                "question": "MIDDLE SCHOOL MURUGAN SPENT MOST TIME AT",
                "answer": "WHAT IS CHALLENGER",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 100
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S FAVORITE SCHOOL SUBJECT",
                "answer": "WHAT IS COMPUTER SCIENCE",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 200
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S FAVORITE TEACHER",
                "answer": "WHO IS MR. BALE",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 300
            },
            {
                "question": "SCHOOL FRIEND MURUGAN HAS KNOWN THE LONGEST",
                "answer": "WHO IS UDAY",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 400
            },
            {
                "question": "PRESCHOOL MURUGAN ATTENDED",
                "answer": "WHAT IS POOKA BEGINNINGS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 500
            }
        ],
        "RANDOM": [
            {
                "question": "CAR MURUGAN DRIVES",
                "answer": "WHAT IS TOYOTA YARIS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 100
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S FAVORITE MUSIC ARTIST",
                "answer": "WHO IS DRAKE",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 200
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S FAVORITE RESTAURANT",
                "answer": "WHAT IS BUFFALO WILD WINGS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 300
            },
            {
                "question": "MURUGAN'S FAVORITE CHILDHOOD VIDEOGAME",
                "answer": "WHAT IS SPY FOX",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 400
            },
            {
                "question": "# OF STATES MURUGAN HAS BEEN TO",
                "answer": "WHAT IS 5 STATES",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 500
            }
        ],
        "COLLEGE": [
            {
                "question": "UNIVERSITY MURUGAN IS GOING TO",
                "answer": "WHAT IS PURDUE",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 100
            },
            {
                "question": "PURDUE MASCOT",
                "answer": "WHAT IS BOILERMAKER",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 200
            },
            {
                "question": "CITY PURDUE IS LOCATED AT",
                "answer": "WHAT IS WEST LAFAYETTE",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 300
            },
            {
                "question": "NAME OF MURUGAN'S ROOMATE",
                "answer": "WHO IS PRANAV CHALLOORI",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 400
            },
            {
                "question": "# OF WING FLAVORS AT PURDUE DINING",
                "answer": "WHAT IS 64 FLAVORS",
                "answered": false,
                "answeredBy": null,
                "answeredCorrectly": null,
                "numPoints": 500
            }
        ]
    },
    "scores": {
        "test1": 0,
        "test2": 0,
        "test3": 0,
        "test4": 0
    }
};